Guide to the International Center for Transitional Justice (ICTJ) records, 1918-2020, bulk 1970-2020 RL.01304
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Records, 1973-2020
  - Administrative Files, 1997-2020
    - Conferences and Events: Audiovisual Materials
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 3), 2009-06-01; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0192)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 4), 2009-06-02; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0193)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 5), 2009-06-02; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0194)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 6), 2009-06-02; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0195)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 7), 2009-06-02; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0196)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 8), 2009-06-03; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0197)
      - Greentree Essentials Course on Transitional Justice (Camera B, Tape 9), 2009-06-03; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0198)
      - ICTJ Book Launch at SSRC "What Happened to the Women", 2007-01-31; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0139)
      - ICTJ Book Launch: Justice as Prevention, 2007-10-31; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0137)
      - ICTJ Book Launch: Justice as Prevention, 2007-10-31; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0138)
      - ICTJ DC Launch (Tutu), 2002-04-08; Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0041)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 1 Day 1, 2008-04-09; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0012)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 1 Day 2, 2008-04-10; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0016)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 2 Day 1, 2008-04-09; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0013)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 2 Day 2, 2008-04-10; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0017)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 3 Day 1, 2008-04-09; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0014)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 3 Day 2, 2008-04-10; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0018)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 4 Day 1, 2008-04-09; Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0015)
      - ICTJ Vineyard Hotel Tape 4 Day 2, 2008-04-10; Cassette (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0019)
      - III Meeting Affinity Group Guatemala, 2005; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0165)
      - International Conference "Building a Future on Peace and Justice", 2007-06-25/2007-06-27; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0221)
        video recording
      - International Conference "Building a Future on Peace and Justice", 2007-06-25/2007-06-27; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0222)
      - International Conference "Building a Future on Peace and Justice", 2007-06-25/2007-06-27; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0223)
      - International Human Rights Law Group Special Forum on Comparative Experiences of Racism, 2001; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0162)
      - International Human Rights Law Group Special Forum on Comparative Experiences of Racism, 2002; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0163)
      - International Law Weekend (Cam A 1), 2006-10-27; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0140)
      - International Law Weekend (Cam A 2), 2006-10-27; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0141)
      - International Law Weekend (Cam B 1), 2006-10-27; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0142)
      - International Seminar on Justice and Reparations for victims of sexual violence in contexts of armed conflict, 2006-08-09/2006-08-10; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0169)
      - Latin American Studies Association International Congress, 2004-10-07/2004-10-09; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0108)
      - Med Conf, 2006 September; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0166)
      - Paige Arthur Seminar NYU (Cam A Tape 1), 2009-01-29; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0092)
      - Paige Arthur Seminar NYU (Cam A Tape 2), 2009-01-29; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0093)
      - Paige Arthur Seminar NYU (Cam B Tape 1), 2009-01-29; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0094)
      - Panel Discussion at NYU-Law, 2008-11-13; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0079)
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 1-3), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0053)
        Conference on Gender Justice in Post-Conflict Situations co-organized by UNIFEM and ILAC
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 13-15), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0056)
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 16-18), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0057)
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 19, Panel 4 edit, part 2 edit, and Pillay, Speaker 5), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0058)
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 4-6), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0054)
      - Peace needs Women and Women need Justice (Tape 7-9), 2004 September; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0055)
      - Photos and videos (processed), 2007-2008; CD (Box 138, Cd RL01304-CD-0217.1-14)
        Photos and videos from events and conferences
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (1), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0113)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (10), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0122)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (11), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0123)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (12), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0124)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (2), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0114)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (3), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0115)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (4), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0116)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (5), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0117)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (6), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0118)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (7), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0119)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (8), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0120)
      - Sisters Arab Forum for Human Rights and ICTJ Conference (9), 2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0121)
      - Stockholm International Forum Conference Series, 2000-2004; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0028)
      - Suocavanje sa Prosloscu, 2002; CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0157)
        in Croatian
      - The 59th Annual DPI/NGO Conference, 2006-09-06/2006-09-08; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0031)
      - Transitional Justice and Human Security Conference (Alex Boraine Speeches), 2005-03-28/2005-04-03; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0037)
      - Transitional Justice and Human Security Conference (part 1), 2005-03-28/2005-04-01; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0035)
      - Transitional Justice and Human Security Conference (part 2), 2005-03-28/2005-04-02; DVD (Box 132, Dvd RL01304-DVD-0036)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 1), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0149)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 2), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0150)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 3), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0151)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 4), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0152)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 5), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0153)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 6), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0154)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera A Tape 7), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0155)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 1), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0156)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 2), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0157)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 3), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0158)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 4), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0159)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 4), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0160)
      - Transitional Justice and Peacebuilding Panel (Camera B Tape 5), 2007-05-15; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0161)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Edited-- "Part 2", Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0281)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Press Briefing, 2004-09-14; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0282)
        Neeleen and Pillay announce conf.
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 1, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0162)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 10, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0171)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 12, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0273)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 13, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0274)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 14, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0275)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 15, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0276)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 16, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0277)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 17, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0278)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 18, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0279)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 19, 2004-09-16; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0280)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 2, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0163)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 3, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0164)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 4, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0165)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 5, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0166)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 6, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0167)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 7, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0168)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 8, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0169)
      - UNIFEM Gender Justice Conference Tape 9, 2004-09-15; Mini-DV (Box 140, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0170)
      - What have we Learned? Panel Discussion (Cam A 1), 2006-09-21; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0086)
      - What have we Learned? Panel Discussion (Cam A 2), 2006-09-21; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0087)
      - What have we Learned? Panel Discussion (Cam B 1), 2006-09-21; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0088)
      - What have we Learned? Panel Discussion (Cam B 2), 2006-09-21; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0089)
    - Conferences and Events Electronic Records, 325 still image (JPEG format), 131 audiovisual (multiple formats), and 32 document (PDF and Microsoft Word formats) files; approximately 67.3 gigabytes. (Digital-materials RL01304-SET-0001)
      Audio recordings of staff lunches and events, International Law Workshop panel discussion with Marieke Wierda, panel discussion with Lemkin's House, Q & A with Graeme about forgiveness, and Yemen Gender Conference.
    - Grants and Fundraising, 1997-2011; 24 folders (Box 116)
      Grants and fundraising proposals, contracts, evaluations, and agreements. Includes Ford Foundation, Rausing Trust, and Andrus Family Fund grants.
    - Budgets, 2009-2011; 5 folders (Box 117)
      Includes reparations program budget, ICTJ budgets, and America's Program budget.
    - Board of Directors, 2001-2012; 61 folders (Box 117-118, 143)
      ICTJ Board of Directors materials. Includes board handbooks, resolutions, expansions and nominations, considerations, bylaws amendments, and the directors handbook. Board of Directors meetings, Executive Committee meetings, President's Report to the Board, and Finance, Administration, and Audit Committee meetings arranged chronologically. Following the board meetings ICTJ Workplans, Strategic Plans, and Budgets arranged chronologically. Box 143 contains board member photos as well as board meeting photos.
    - Staff Development, 2001-2008; 4 folders (Box 119)
      Oversize staff retreat posters. Banner from a conference in Nepal and missing persons drawings for a truth commission workshop.
    - International Center for Transitional Justice website, 2012-2020; 2012-
    - International Center for Transitional Justice News, 2013-2020; 2013-ongoing
    - International Center for Transitional Justice YouTube, 2012-2020; 2012-ongoing
    - International Center for Transitional Justice Facebook account, 2012-2020; 2012-ongoing
    - International Center for Transitional Justice Twitter account, 2012-2020; 2012-ongoing
- Audiovisual Materials
  Contains assorted audiovisual material generated by ICTJ. This series contains audiovisual materials that are either unlabeled or that do not provide enough information to place them in the existing series. These materials are of several formats including CD, DVD, cassette tape, miniDV, VHS and betamax tape.
  Collection contains fragile audiovisual/photographic formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 1, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0001)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 10, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0010)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 11, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0011)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 2, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0002)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 3, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0003)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 4, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0004)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 5, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0005)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 6, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0006)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 7, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0007)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 8, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0008)
  - International Center for Transitional Justice Tape 9, Cassette (Box 133, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0009)
  - 101 East, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0004)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 1, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0067)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 2, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0068)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 3, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0069)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 4, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0070)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 5, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0071)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 6, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0072)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 7, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0073)
  - 24-04-01 Tape 8, 2001-04-24; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0074)
  - BBC World TU, VHS (Box 127, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0144)
  - Bellagio Tape 1, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0066)
  - Bishop P. Buckle, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0003)
  - CDF Trial Opening; RUF opening, 2004-06-07; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0013)
  - Clips from VHS-Witness to Truth, Calling the Ghosts, Nyameka's Story, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0020)
  - Day One Contd, VHS (Box 127, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0135)
  - Done 4, Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0040)
  - F10, VHS (Box 127, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0150)
  - F9, VHS (Box 127, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0159)
  - For notes, Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0036)
  - Gem Erskine, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0002)
  - Hacia la Construccion de Estrategias Contra la Impunidad, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0182)
  - ICTJ Fireworks, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0035)
  - International Coalition of Historic Sites of Conscience, VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0071)
  - Kaset I Galch, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0053)
  - Kaset II Galch, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0052)
  - M.W. Adams and Gen. Erskine, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0027)
  - Medicine Men, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0190)
  - Notes 3, Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0039)
  - Otunba Durojaiye/GC Oyewde, VHS (Box 127, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0141)
  - Paul Vensele, 2003-06-26; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0024)
  - Peace by Peace Reel 1 of 1, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0049)
  - Photographs Palace of Justice, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0155)
  - Prof. M Bonsu, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0004)
  - Reficassid 1-4 Episode 1-8, VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0077)
  - Reflets I, cassette 3, VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0072)
  - Relets I episodes 8 a 12, Cassette (Box 134, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0033)
  - Robben Island Our University, VHS (Box 128, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0193)
    James Agee Film Project: a Non-Profit Corp
  - Salomon Lernz Fevres, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0057)
  - Scpt's Children Rough Cut, 2004-06-25; VHS (Box 123, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0022)
  - SL TRC, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0036)
    it says SL TRC but that is crossed out
  - Spots Radiales 1, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0066)
  - Spots Radiales 2, CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0067)
  - Syllabus DIPDEM, 2006-2007; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0030)
  - The Arusha Tapes, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0007)
    Dubbed from VHS
  - The Story, VHS (Box 125, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0078)
  - The Terror and the Truth, VHS (Box 126, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0109)
    NTSC copy
  - The Terror and the Truth, VHS (Box 126, Video-cassette RL01304-VHS-0110)
    PAL copy
  - Tomaschut Interview, 2003-07-22; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0001)
  - Tomuscha (tape 21), Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0023)
  - Trece Anos, CD (Box 137, Cd RL01304-CD-0150)
  - Trials and Tribunals Kimmel, 2003-11-05; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0064)
  - Trials and Tribunals Kimmel, 2004-11-05; Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0065)
  - Untitled, Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0038)
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0075)
  - Untitled, Cassette (Box 135, Audio-cassette RL01304-CS-0037)
    Possibly a blank tape
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0031)
    Potentially blank
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0032)
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0033)
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0034)
  - Untitled, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0037)
  - VO Carlos and Salomon, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0005)
  - Washington Forum "Chad-Sudan", 2009-05-14; CD (Box 136, Cd RL01304-CD-0007)
  - Yasmine Sooka, Mini-DV (Box 139, Video-cassette RL01304-MDV-0018)